{
  "GroupId": 1,
  "GroupName": "FRANCE",
  "Levels": [
    {
      "GroupId": 1,
      "LevelId": 1,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "SHEEP",
          "question": "Farm animal known for wool"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "GUIDE",
          "question": "Person who leads tours"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "MAFIA",
          "question": "Organized crime syndicate"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "BUFFY",
          "question": "Vampire slayer's first name"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "CHESS",
          "question": "Game with knights and queens"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "RELAX",
          "question": "Unwind or take it easy"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "PHOTO",
          "question": "Snapshot taken with a camera"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "IDIOT",
          "question": "Foolish or senseless person"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "BROWN",
          "question": "Color associated with chocolate or autumn leaves"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "CAMEL",
          "question": "Desert animal known for its humps"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "SHORT",
          "question": "Not tall; lacking in height"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 0,
          "answer_text": "EIFFEL TOWER",
          "question": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "GroupId": 1,
      "LevelId": 2,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "BANNER",
          "question": "Wave it high, words in the sky; symbol of pride that catches the eye"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "STEADY",
          "question": "Not in a rush, a constant flow"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "SUPPLY",
          "question": "Stock and demand, a constant affair"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "SMOOTH",
          "question": "a surface so plump"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "EAGLES",
          "question": "Soaring high with eyes so keen, rulers of the sky"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "LABELS",
          "question": "Stuck on products, names they bear; identifying marks"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "LABOUR",
          "question": "The grind, the sweat, the daily strife"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "EARNED",
          "question": "Not given, but hard-fought gain; fruits of labor, not in vain"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "ZAREBA",
          "question": "Thorns and posts in a guarded spree"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "NARROW",
          "question": "Thin passage, tight and restricted; not wide"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "MARINE",
          "question": "Blue expanse, a vast scene; salty waves and hues serene"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "FLORAL",
          "question": "Petals dance in nature's gown, fragrant blooms"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "CRUMPS",
          "question": "Small bits, fragments, a scattered sum"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "UPLOAD",
          "question": "Ascend to the digital sphere; send data soaring, crystal clear"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "CENTRE",
          "question": "Middle point, focal grace"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "BEASTS",
          "question": "Creatures wild, with fur or feather"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "APPLES",
          "question": "a crunchy treat; red, green, or gold, they're good to eat"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 0,
          "answer_text": "NAPOLEON BONAPARTE",
          "question": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "GroupId": 1,
      "LevelId": 3,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "EFFECTS",
          "question": "Transformations observed, changes detected"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "PRIVATE",
          "question": "Restricted access, secrecy's embrace"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "REGIONS",
          "question": "Divisions defined, within borders, cultures converse"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "ANSWERS",
          "question": "solutions found, sought in puzzles"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "ACCOUNT",
          "question": "Tracks every cent, where money flows"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "CHEATED",
          "question": "Deception's sting, trust betrayed"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "ARRANGE",
          "question": "Order in chaos, tidy array; jumble no more, sequence at bay"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "ELEMENT",
          "question": "nature's core; building blocks, in all things stored"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "INVOLVE",
          "question": "Participation required, engagement sought"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "BROTHER",
          "question": "Sibling bond, kinship true; through thick and thin"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "CULTURE",
          "question": "Customs shared, heritage held; in every tale"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "JOURNEY",
          "question": "Paths unfold, adventures begun; through trials and triumphs"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "BATTERY",
          "question": "Power stored, energy's might; fueling devices"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "EDITION",
          "question": "Variant release, content refined; updated version"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "BROUGHT",
          "question": "Carried along, from there to here; delivered, without a fear"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "CENTURY",
          "question": "Ten decades gone, history's thread; a hundred years"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 0,
          "answer_text": "FRENCH REVOLUTION",
          "question": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "GroupId": 1,
      "LevelId": 4,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "BLUSH",
          "question": "Rosy cheeks, shy display; emotions bloom in a subtle way."
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "BONUS",
          "question": "Extra gain, a pleasant surprise; reward beyond the usual guise"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "FUNNY",
          "question": "Laughs provoked, humor's charm; joy found in a comic arm"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "EVENT",
          "question": "Gatherings held, moments prime; memories made"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "BRICK",
          "question": "Building block, sturdy and thick"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "DEATH",
          "question": "Life's finale, inevitable end; farewell to all"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "ADMIN",
          "question": "Behind the scenes, managing all; overseeing tasks"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "ADULT",
          "question": "Grown and mature, responsibilities hold;"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "WASTE",
          "question": "Discarded excess, resources lost; in disposal bins"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "AGENT",
          "question": "Acting on behalf, missions pursue; catalyst for change"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "BRUSH",
          "question": "Sweeping strokes, canvas grace; painting tool"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "LEMON",
          "question": "Yellow and tart, citrus delight; zesty flavor"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 0,
          "answer_text": "LOUVRE MUSEUM",
          "question": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "GroupId": 1,
      "LevelId": 5,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "DOCTOR",
          "question": "Healer of ailments, keeper of health"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "COHORT",
          "question": "Group in stride, united role; companions in aim"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "EMAILS",
          "question": "Digital letters, swift and light; inbox filled"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "MARKET",
          "question": "Hub of commerce, goods exchange; buyers and sellers"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "KILLED",
          "question": "Life's end, abruptly stilled; tragedy strikes"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "BREADS",
          "question": "Oven-fresh loaves, aroma divine; staple sustenance"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "BASKET",
          "question": "Carrying loads, woven grace; holding treasures"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "BUDGET",
          "question": "Finances planned, expenses set; within limits"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "ENERGY",
          "question": "Power within, vibrant force; driving motion"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "NUGGET",
          "question": "Tiny treasure, precious find; gleaming gold"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "ATTACK",
          "question": "Sudden strike, aggression shown; defense required"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "BEAUTY",
          "question": "Aesthetic grace, sight's delight; in nature's art"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "YELLOW",
          "question": "Sunny hue, vibrant and bold; daffodils bloom"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "BALLON",
          "question": "Floating high, colorful sphere; tethered dreams"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "CLIENT",
          "question": "Service seeker, needs to fulfill; patron of goods"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 0,
          "answer_text": "CHARLES DE GAULLE",
          "question": null
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}